<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Amelia Lewis</title><atom:link href="http://amelia.design/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link>http://amelia.design</link><description>Portfolio of Amelia Lewis</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><generator>Wintersmith - https://github.com/jnordberg/wintersmith</generator><language>en</language><item><title>Stipple Design System</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/stipple-design-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/stipple-design-system/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;As the first full-time designer dedicated to the Wall Street Journal’s newsroom tools, I had the unique opportunity to take ownership over the suite and reimagine the designs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;sketch-libraries&quot;&gt;Sketch Libraries&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;documentation&quot;&gt;Documentation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;react-component-library&quot;&gt;React Component Library&lt;/h2&gt;
</description></item><item><title>Newsroom Editorial Tools</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/newsroom-editorial-tools/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/newsroom-editorial-tools/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;newsgrid&quot;&gt;NewsGrid&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I joined the team at WSJ, my first task was to jump on a moving train that was set out to revolutionize how news is planned for the website and the paper each day. Prior to NewsGrid, planning was done in a number of different ways around the newsroom—souped-up Google Sheets, group emails, Post-It notes, whiteboards—you name it. With a newsroom of around 1,200 people spread across dozens of global offices, this meant that news planning was essentially a big ol’ mess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Planning is important not only for the print paper, but to also make decisions for digital coverage through the day and for off-platform publishing including social media and Apple News+. The Journal publishes over 100 stories a day, a good portion of which are not breaking news—reporters can work on a story for weeks or months in advance—and so the need to plan that coverage is key.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/newsroom-editorial-tools/newsgrid-weekly.png&quot; alt=&quot;Weekly planning view in NewsGrid&quot; title=&quot;Weekly planning view in NewsGrid&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NewsGrid allows users to create a story, to which they can attach some key dates and flags to it, along with any planned assets. They can collaborate across the newsroom in one centralized place. NewsGrid’s users include reporters, editors, coverage and bureau chiefs, publishing and platform editors, podcast and video producers, and the Editor in Chief.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/newsroom-editorial-tools/newsgrid-buro.png&quot; alt=&quot;Bureau planning view in NewsGrid&quot; title=&quot;Bureau planning view in NewsGrid&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;authoring&quot;&gt;Authoring&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;charts&quot;&gt;Charts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a business publication, charts are an essential part of the visuals presented with most articles. Charts and data are often the main thing a reader looks for in the Wall Street Journal—especially online—so having clear, readable and interactive charts is key to the newsroom. Prior to joining, the newsroom tools team had built a new charting tool that utilized &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.highcharts.com&quot;&gt;Highcharts&lt;/a&gt;, as well as both custom data and market data. Functionally the tool was great, but it had been built scrappily, and without a designer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;image-manager&quot;&gt;Image Manager&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;news-alerts&quot;&gt;News Alerts&lt;/h2&gt;
</description></item><item><title>Rupert Graves</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/rupert-graves/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/rupert-graves/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;Rupert is an actor based in the UK with a decades-long resume under his belt. While his old, fan-maintained website was &lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20161011054251/https://www.rupert-graves.com/&quot;&gt;truly glorious&lt;/a&gt;, 2019 meant time for a change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I designed and built the site myself from scratch, using &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/rupert-graves/new-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Home Page&quot; title=&quot;Home Page&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Home page&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/rupert-graves/new-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Listing Page&quot; title=&quot;Listing Page&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Listing page&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/rupert-graves/old.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Old Site&quot; title=&quot;Old Site&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;R.I.P. you special, special website&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>Greekify</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/greekify/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/greekify/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;Coming Soon&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>Rivendell Design System</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/rivendell-design-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/rivendell-design-system/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;foundations&quot;&gt;Foundations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WeWork’s &lt;a href=&quot;http://digital-foundations.netlify.com/&quot;&gt;Digital Foundations&lt;/a&gt; seek to unify the design language across all of the company’s digital properties. The evolution of these foundations for the wework.com is the &lt;a href=&quot;http://rivendell-docs.netlify.com/&quot;&gt;Rivendell&lt;/a&gt; design system. While the foundations include elements such as color, typography, tone of voice and accessibility guidelines, Rivendell takes those to the next level with a set of reusable components and patterns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;patterns&quot;&gt;Patterns&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rivendell covers everything from button and input styles, to color and text style systems. These core components were then used to create reusable, but modifiable, content block patterns for the site. Based on weeks of auditing the existing site, we determined a list of roughly 20 patterns that would be used to restyle the bulk of the content on wework.com. Over the years (and incredibly fast growth), the website had definitely fallen victim to a few too many button styles and logo grids.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/rivendell-design-system/foundations-text-title-impact.png&quot; alt=&quot;Impact Title Styles&quot; title=&quot;Impact Title Styles&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/rivendell-design-system/components-buttons.png&quot; alt=&quot;Button Styles&quot; title=&quot;Button Styles&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visually, the goal was to create something that was rather paired back and simple, so as to give a fresh new look that we could continue to evolve and build upon. We always want to make sure the design on the digital side of WeWork reflects the beautiful, open, light-filled feel of our spaces. Color and typography are purposely used scarcely, to allow the focus to fall onto the imagery of our spaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea was that the patterns would almost be “plug and play” blocks that anyone could use to quickly and easily create a beautiful page. Creating a uniformed spacing system was key, so that the patterns could be stacked in any order and look great next to each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/rivendell-design-system/media-caption.png&quot; alt=&quot;Media &amp;amp; Caption&quot; title=&quot;Media &amp;amp; Caption&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/rivendell-design-system/masthead-3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Masthead #3&quot; title=&quot;Masthead #3&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/rivendell-design-system/bottom-bar.png&quot; alt=&quot;Sticky Bottom Bar&quot; title=&quot;Sticky Bottom Bar&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/rivendell-design-system/cross-sells.png&quot; alt=&quot;Cross Sells&quot; title=&quot;Cross Sells&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;responsiveness-and-accessibility&quot;&gt;Responsiveness and Accessibility&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The patterns had to be robust, flexible and responsive. WeWork supports over 10 locales, so the patterns had to support any length of copy, and also make sense when localized (coming soon: right-to-left languages!). The patterns also had to be responsive to any viewport width or device type, as our users are split almost 50/50 across desktop and mobile, and I stressed tested the patterns vigorously to make sure all screen sizes were tended to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With WeWork’s ever-expanding audience, another high priority element of Rivendell was accessibility. We are dedicated to making sure the system is AA compliant—meaning colors were readable, inputs had labels, HTML syntax made sense, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;prototyping&quot;&gt;Prototyping&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To enable rapid prototyping (and some out-of-hours design exploration), I built this &lt;a href=&quot;http://amelia.design/articles/rivendell-design-system/%22http://ww-styleguide.amelia-lewis.com/style-guide&quot;&gt;style guide&lt;/a&gt; from scratch in my own environment. I also used it as a chance to &lt;a href=&quot;http://ww-styleguide.amelia-lewis.com/&quot;&gt;prototype&lt;/a&gt; what wework.com will look like once Rivendell is fully rolled out. Actually building the patterns with HTML/CSS allowed me to further test the responsiveness of the patterns&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;integration&quot;&gt;Integration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the last few months, I have led the integration and roll-out of Rivendell onto &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wework.com/&quot;&gt;wework.com&lt;/a&gt;. It’s still a work in progress, but you can see that the core components, such as buttons, inputs and text styles, have been rolled out, and the patterns are slowly coming through too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://roomfive.net/&quot;&gt;Andrew Couldwell&lt;/a&gt; was the lead and creative director for the Rivendell design system.&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>WeWork Guest Wi-Fi</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/wework-guest-wifi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/wework-guest-wifi/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;In late-2017, WeWork’s marketing team was presented with a great opportunity to set up guest wi-fi in all locations. The was beneficial both for the user, to help them learn more about WeWork (and get wi-fi), but also for the business to acquire leads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I worked closely with internal stakeholders and with the team at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.socialsign.in/&quot;&gt;SocialSign.in&lt;/a&gt; to design the look and feel of the flow, and then I wrote the CSS to integrate the styles. The design of the experience obviously had to be optimized for both mobile and desktop, as there are any number of reasons—work-related or not—that somoene may be in a WeWork. The guest wi-fi also, for the first time ever, gives WeWork an opportunity to find out more about these reasons. For a user who may be less familiar with the brand, we’ve put in some handy information for how to interact with the space and learn more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are rolling out the experience globally, adding new languages and locales every month. Thus far we have launched in the US, Canada, Latin America and Europe. The launch so far has been considered extremely successful. In just the first month-and-a-half, over 50,000 users logged into the guest wi-fi, and 82% of those people were new leads. To date, gated wi-fi has contributed to over 500 desks sold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wework-guest-wifi/guest-wifi-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Guest Wi-Fi&quot; title=&quot;Guest Wi-Fi&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wework-guest-wifi/guest-wifi-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Guest Wi-Fi&quot; title=&quot;Guest Wi-Fi&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wework-guest-wifi/guest-wifi-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Guest Wi-Fi&quot; title=&quot;Guest Wi-Fi&quot;&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wework-guest-wifi/guest-wifi-mobile.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Guest Wi-Fi&quot; title=&quot;Guest Wi-Fi&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>WeWork.com</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/wework-dot-com/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/wework-dot-com/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;Coming Soon&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>Insight</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/wgsn-insight/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/wgsn-insight/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;October 1st, 2016 marked the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wgsn.com/en/article/wgsn-launches-wgsn-insight-consumer-market-intelligence-product/?lang=en&quot;&gt;launch&lt;/a&gt; of a brand new product for WGSN; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wgsn.com/en/products/insight/&quot;&gt;WGSN Insight&lt;/a&gt;. Following the form and function of our flagship product, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wgsn.com/en/products/fashion/&quot;&gt;WGSN Fashion&lt;/a&gt;, Insight couples big-picture thinking with immediate insight into the ever-evolving consumer your brand serves, including intelligence and research on the latest technology, marketing and retail innovations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Insight also marked the introduction of our new branding to our users; a marked step forward in the visuals and user experience of our products. It was on my suggestion that we did this. While I was not initially involved in this project, I did join closer to the end of the design phase in order to reskin the designs with the new branding, and remained heavily invovled through development to make sure the designs were executed well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Insight was also WGSN’s first responsive product. Rather than producing dozens of designs for every screen size, I created this &lt;a href=&quot;http://wgsn-think-tank.amelia-lewis.com/&quot;&gt;prototype&lt;/a&gt; to demonstate to the developers how I wanted responsiveness to work&amp;mdash;I always find something that moves to be far more useful in this scenario.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-insight/wgsn-insight-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Insight&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Insight&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Home page&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-insight/wgsn-insight-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Insight&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Insight&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Listing page&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-insight/wgsn-insight-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Insight&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Insight&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Content report&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another thing that was important to me with Insight (and the new branding in general), was to include little delights like fancy hover states. The interfaces, in general, are on the simpler side, so I think it’s nice to show a little extra thought and care with these to “wow” our users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-insight/wgsn-insight-4.gif&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Insight&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Insight&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Hover state&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Insight launch was really &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wgsn.com/blogs/5-reasons-why-you-will-love-wgsn-insight&quot;&gt;successful&lt;/a&gt;, from both a product/tech standpoint and also a sales one. Anticipation of the launch drove sales to record highs and we had almost no tech hiccups during, or post-launch. By all accounts, our users are absolutely loving the product.&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>City by City App</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/wgsn-city-by-city-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/wgsn-city-by-city-app/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;City by City is one of WGSN’s staple sub-products, used heavily by the core group of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wgsn.com/en/products/fashion/&quot;&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wgsn.com/en/products/lifestyle-interiors/&quot;&gt;Lifestyle &amp;amp; Interiors&lt;/a&gt; customers. It is somewhat of an editor-curated Yelp; hand-picked shopping, dining, accomodation and sightseeing choices from top cities around the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2016, it finally came time to call time of death on the old version of the app (built around iOS 6 era), and fit in a rebuild and reskin. The tech team decided to rebuild from scratch using &lt;a href=&quot;https://facebook.github.io/react-native/&quot;&gt;React Native&lt;/a&gt; so that we could package the same app for iOS and Android (and because we do not have iOS or Android developers in-house). The functionality of the app was to stay in tact, but since we were doing the rebuild, it only made sense to give the visuals a bit of a refresh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since this happened right around the time our rebrand was being discussed, I purposely kept the visuals as simple as possible to allow for an easy update in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In both the desktop product and the app, users are able to view and filter through place listings, browse through the biggest cities in the world and create their own maps and itineraries, filled with their top to-dos as recommended by our editors. We did our best to keep each of these user interactions and patterns inline with similar apps like Yelp, Google or TripAdvisor so that there was no space for confusion or difficulty of use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;clickable-prototype&quot;&gt;Clickable Prototype&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;438&quot; height=&quot;930&quot; src=&quot;//invis.io/G37EZPKXS&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;


</description></item><item><title>WGSN Marketing Site</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/wgsn-marketing-site/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/wgsn-marketing-site/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-marketing-site/wgsn-public-site-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Public Site&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Public Site&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I started at &lt;a href=&quot;http://wgsn.com/&quot;&gt;WGSN&lt;/a&gt;, the product and marketing teams were already well into the redesign of their non-subscriber site. The goal was to refresh the look of the site and pull together the various product sites under the new “single platform” approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flat designs for the desktop version of the site were done, and my task was to turn these into responsive designs that could work across all screens and devices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;making-a-desktop-site-responsive&quot;&gt;Making a Desktop Site Responsive&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The existing designs had been done for a larger desktop screen, so various elements had to be adjusted in order to make them more modular and able be to transformed between all different screen sizes. I really wanted the site to be completely fluid, not just fixed to a handful of breakpoints. Some elements made for easy, obvious transitions, while others had to be tweaked on the larger screens in order to make for a smarter transition into the smaller screens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though this was a marketing/brochure site, I still wanted there to be a strongly held design system in place. This site redesign marked the beginning of a new look and feel for all our other WGSN products and it was important to put a strong foot forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;prototyping&quot;&gt;Prototyping&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to most effectively communicate how I wanted the site to behave between different screen sizes, I put together a &lt;a href=&quot;http://wgsn-public-site.amelia-lewis.com/&quot;&gt;prototype&lt;/a&gt;. This was built from scratch using &lt;a href=&quot;https://harpjs.com/&quot;&gt;Harp.js&lt;/a&gt; and ended up being rather high-fidelity as a I had a lot of time to work on it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The prototype proved to be very useful, as we were working with developers overseas to build the site, so it was a great way to get the details across to them. It also proved very useful for the art department to try out different imagery easily before having the proper site and CMS built.&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>Workspace and Image Library</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/wgsn-workspace/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/wgsn-workspace/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;WGSN’s Image &amp;amp; Design Library is where subscribers can access our database of over 20 million exclusive images and design resources. Workspace is where they can save and organize all their favorite content from sections of the site including Image &amp;amp; Design Library, often a core part of their workflow. Both of these products have been untouched for around 8 years, and at the beginning of 2016 we begun the process of a full redesign and rebuild.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Full case study coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-workspace/wgsn-workspace-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Workspace&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-workspace/wgsn-workspace-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Selection mode&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-workspace/wgsn-workspace-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Image library&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-workspace/wgsn-workspace-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Search autocomplete&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-workspace/wgsn-workspace-5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Tagging and filtering&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-workspace/wgsn-workspace-6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Advanced filtering&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-workspace/wgsn-workspace-7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Image viewer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-workspace/wgsn-workspace-8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Save to workspace&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-workspace/wgsn-workspace-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Workspace &amp;amp; Image Library&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Print&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>Catwalks App</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/wgsn-catwalks-app/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/wgsn-catwalks-app/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;Catwalk coverage is key to &lt;a href=&quot;http://wgsn.com/&quot;&gt;WGSN&lt;/a&gt;‘s offering so extending that out into a mobile app was the obvious next step forward for our customers’ Fashion Week experience. Collections from New York, London, Milan and Paris Fashion Weeks are fed through almost instantly so our users are able to stay completely up-to-the-minute with the latest looks and expert analyses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As well as the latest shows, we wanted users to be able to search and filter through older collections, and save images to their Workspaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;starting-fresh&quot;&gt;Starting Fresh&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We were starting on a clean slate for the Catwalks App, both for this app itself, and for the family of apps we knew we wanted to do after this. This meant thinking about a scalable UI and following best practices for both iOS and Android.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My role in the initial version of this project was wire framing and interaction design&amp;mdash;deciding how the screen flow and content layout should work, as well as the interactions and transitions throughout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For what seemed like such a simple app, some complexities arose regarding the way a user interacts with their workspace (which is not currently mobile-friendly), and the way we displayed and filtered through the collections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-catwalks-app/wgsn-catwalks-app-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Catwalks App&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Catwalks App&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-catwalks-app/wgsn-catwalks-app-3.png&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Catwalks App&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Catwalks App&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through the visual design process, I played more of backseat role, mostly providing feedback to our visual designer and helping him shape the overall look and feel of the product. We were trying to create a slightly different feel to the rest of the branding, aiming for something that felt higher-end and more exclusive. He achieved this with the darker color scheme, more use of the serif font and the full-bleed images.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The app, while only accessible to WGSN subscribers, was launched successfully in time for the January 2016 catwalk season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;phase-two&quot;&gt;Phase Two&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More recently, I started working on designs for our &lt;a href=&quot;http://amelia.design/articles/wgsn-city-by-city-app&quot;&gt;City by City App&lt;/a&gt; (CxC) as well as working on a feature update for this app, and from the beginning it was clear that we needed to define a stronger visual style guide for our apps to make them all feel like part of a family, and more like they were following iOS and Android design patterns and standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aside from a number of small visual tweaks&amp;mdash;mostly along the lines of typography and spacing&amp;mdash;the biggest change to make in the Catwalks App was around the navigation. Originally, we had chosen to go with a hamburger menu, as that’s what we do in all our web products, and it seemed the obvious choice. Upon doing more research for CxC, we came to the conclusion that a bottom tab bar was a more preferable solution for usability and scalability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phase 2 is still waiting to be worked on by our developers, but will hopefully be launched in time for the catwalks season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;![WGSN Catwalks App](wgsn-catwalks-app-5.jpg “WGSN Catwalks App” data-lightbox=”wgsn-catwalks-app”)&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>Rebrand and Style Guide</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/wgsn-rebrand-and-styleguide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/wgsn-rebrand-and-styleguide/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;The WGSN style guide began as a simple tool for myself from which to grab the colors and logos for all our products. After a few months at WGSN, however, it became apparent there was no solid structure or style guide for how we were designing our products. Every UI element was being designed and coded over and over… always slightly differently. So, I took it upon myself to start creating a full style guide for the WGSN product team. The company also began a big rebrand project around this time, putting us in the perfect position to think about redesigning every UI element.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-rebrand-and-styleguide/wgsn-brand-guide-9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Color system tool&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taking inspiration from sites like Dropbox’s &lt;a href=&quot;http://dropbox.github.io/scooter/index.html&quot;&gt;Scooter&lt;/a&gt; and Marvel’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://marvelapp.com/styleguide/overview/introduction&quot;&gt;Style Guide&lt;/a&gt;, I started compiling a full set of UI components and styles used around the site and constructed them into guidelines and reusable components.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I worked on the style guide alongside designing an actual product&amp;mdash;which proved to be very useful, for both things&amp;mdash;and created all these elements, or “building blocks”, which we could use from then on to design all our products. It was important that these elements were reusable across different screens, platforms and contexts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-rebrand-and-styleguide/wgsn-brand-guide-11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Text styles&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-rebrand-and-styleguide/wgsn-brand-guide-12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Content tile&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-rebrand-and-styleguide/wgsn-brand-guide-13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Buttons&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-rebrand-and-styleguide/wgsn-brand-guide-14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Inputs&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-rebrand-and-styleguide/wgsn-brand-guide-15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Cards&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/wgsn-rebrand-and-styleguide/wgsn-brand-guide-16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot; title=&quot;WGSN Brand Guide&quot;&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Carousel&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project is as much about front-end development as it is design. A very important part of this is setting standards for the CSS we write as a team, and consolidating all the components that we’ve historically written over and over again. Through the entire preocess, I’ve been working closely with the front-end developers to ensure everything I’m making works well for them and their code bases. Similarly, I’ve made sure to closely involve our creative services teams to make sure our products are tied in nicely with any marketing collateral our users see.&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>The Blending Room</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/the-blending-room/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/the-blending-room/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jrcigars.com/&quot;&gt;JR Cigars&lt;/a&gt; is the world’s largest cigar e-commerce site, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://creativelicence.com.au/&quot;&gt;CLD&lt;/a&gt; recently redesigned and rebuilt their platform. While I didn’t play a huge role in the site design, I did do a number of feature updates and changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jrcigars.com/blending-room/&quot;&gt;The Blending Room&lt;/a&gt; is a new content hub for JR’s customers to get access to everything they need to know about cigars, latest news and events, video reviews and intgrated social media feeds. This type of content experiences very high traffic on the current site and is great for SEO, so The Blending Room was conceived as a way to really consolidate all that content in its own, dedicated place and enrich the user experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Blending Room is a Wordpress site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-approach&quot;&gt;My Approach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was brought onto this project as design lead well into the content and basic layout decisions, but was essentially given free reign to make the space as visually interesting and exciting as possible. While remaining within the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jrcigars.com/styleguide&quot;&gt;JR Branding&lt;/a&gt;, I was able to make &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jrcigars.com/blending-room/&quot;&gt;The Blending Room&lt;/a&gt; a little more fun and “edgier” than the very conservative look and feel of the e-commerce site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To make the experience as rich and exciting as possible, I kept the design very image centric. This allowed the client and their editorial team to support their content with great assets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was the first time I’d even touched Wordpress, and while at first I was somewhat daunted, once I got my head around it all it was actually quite a smooth process. I was, however, largely working with already existing CSS styles and templates from the main site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/the-blending-room/the-blending-room-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Blending Room&quot; title=&quot;The Blending Room&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>Field InTouch</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/field-intouch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/field-intouch/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;Field InTouch is a versatile, modular platform providing sales forces with a single application for their core needs in the field. It is an iPad app and platform developed by &lt;a href=&quot;http://creativelicence.com.au/&quot;&gt;CLD&lt;/a&gt;, and I regularly produced interactive slidedecks/mini-apps that are housed within in the app while I was there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the time I was at &lt;a href=&quot;http://creativelicence.com.au/&quot;&gt;CLD&lt;/a&gt;, we worked consistently to make these decks more and more impressive, and our clients loved them. Through FiT, they are able to get otherwise unattainable analytics about their field force and the force is able to enjoy their sales material with levels of interactivity and excitement just not achievable by their traditional means and resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The majority of the work I did was for our largest client, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imperial-tobacco.com/&quot;&gt;Imperial Tobacco&lt;/a&gt;. My work was used all around the world and I localised decks for the U.S, the U.K., Australia, New Zealand, France, Belgium, the Netherlands, Estonia, Saudi Arabia, UAE and Iraq.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-approach&quot;&gt;My Approach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I was generally working with branding dictated by the client/brand, I was able to push the boundaries with the visuals in order to make the decks as fun and exciting for the reps and their audiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In these decks, the content is generally the promotion of a new product or feature, so my role was initially to come up with creative concepts for ways to represent this information, including questions with interactive answer mechanics and simple games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Technically, I was responsible for creating the entire front-end of each deck. I got to have a lot of fun experimenting with cool CSS features and animations, while still being careful to optimise for older generation iPads as well as newer ones. The FiT decks are Brunch apps, utilising Jade, Sass and CoffeeScript.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/field-intouch/field-intouch-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Field InTouch&quot; title=&quot;Field InTouch&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>Cosentyx Let's Go</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/cosentyx-lets-go/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/cosentyx-lets-go/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;Let’s Go is an iOS app I’m currently working on. It’s a place for Psoriasis patents who use the drug Cosentyx to find support and information about their condition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The process has been a little tricky, as the brief has continued to change throughout to meet the needs of various teams within Novartis, but we have now settled on both the content and visual design. Let’s Go is a native iOS app for iPhone and iPad, and is about half way through development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-approach&quot;&gt;My Approach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The design process for Let’s Go has been a bit unusual because I was given (dated) designs for an existing app, which is now forming a section of our app, as well as a new set of branding which included the rainbow bursts pictured above. I absolutely loved the rainbow bursts and knew they had to be worked into the designs in a great way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I’ve kept a lot of the UI elements very simple, I’ve really enjoyed being able to play around with the bright colours and fun imagery. The purpose of the app is really to collect a lot of data about the patient in order to help with their condition, so we had to think of creative ways for the user to interact with these inputs and want to keep coming back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A big challenge I’m facing is designing the layouts for iPad. Most of the screens don’t have lots of content, so it’s been interesting reworking the designs for the much bigger screen real estate while keeping them looking good, practical and useful.&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>Momo Brasserie</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/momo-brasserie/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/momo-brasserie/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;Coming soon&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>RepAssist</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/repassist/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2014 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/repassist/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;RepAssist was a pre-existing iPhone app that &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.novartis.com/&quot;&gt;Novartis&lt;/a&gt; had, and they came to us at &lt;a href=&quot;http://creativelicence.com.au/&quot;&gt;CLD&lt;/a&gt; asking to rebuild the thing from the ground up. The old one was&amp;mdash;to put it delicately&amp;mdash;in dire need of a redesign.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The app is used by sales reps for two functions; to submit expense reports for events they’ve held, and to order drug samples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The app was released internally within Novartis and has received excellent reviews.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-approach&quot;&gt;My Approach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The UX and user flow of this app was probably one of the more complicated I’ve dealt with beacuse of the sheer volume of form inputs, most of which weren’t super easy to split into neat categories, and the client’s request to make these relatively mundane tasks “fun”. We spent weeks going back and forth between layouts and ways to arrange the content before finally settling on a horizontal-swipe card layout (which, later, proved to not be the most scalable decision).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In terms of visual design, I chose to keep the interface as clean and simple as possible to balance out the content-heavy screens. I kept the colour palette largely to white and greys, only using Novartis’ brand colours sparingly, always with the purpose of providing information to the user about their input in the form of error messages and buttons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/repassist/repassist.png&quot; alt=&quot;RepAssist&quot; title=&quot;RepAssist&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>Meat Cuts</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/meat-cuts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2014 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/meat-cuts/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;Meat Cuts is an app I worked on at &lt;a href=&quot;http://creativelicence.com.au/&quot;&gt;CLD&lt;/a&gt;, briefed by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mla.com.au/Home&quot;&gt;Meat &amp;amp; Livestock Australia&lt;/a&gt;. They wanted to create an app for users to learn all about various cuts of meat and how best to cook them, in a fun an interactive way. Our target user group was gourmet home cooks&amp;mdash;largely, but not exclusively, in the young male demographic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were a number of apps with a similar function on the App Store, so we really wanted Meat Cuts to stand out visually and to be the one that users chose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The app has been downloaded over 60,000 times on both iOS and Android, with mostly 4 and 5 star reviews.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-approach&quot;&gt;My Approach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was the first project at &lt;a href=&quot;http://creativelicence.com.au/&quot;&gt;CLD&lt;/a&gt; where I was able to take the lead on the design and art direction, as well as being the first consumer app I really worked on. The client’s only real design input was that they wanted a “chalkboard look”, so I got to have a lot of fun taking ownership of both the UX/user flow and the visual design.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With feedback from my colleagues, I decided to keep both the user flow and the visuals as clean and simple as possible, while still taking care to integrate some interesting line work and imagery evocative of that chalkboard feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The biggest challenge I faced in the design of Meat Cuts was fitting the animal diagrams onto the small screens, while keeping them large enough for the smaller sections to be tappable. We experimented with various device-rotation ideas, but in the end decided a horizontal scroll was the most user-friendly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meat Cuts was built as a hybrid web app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/meat-cuts/meat-cuts.png&quot; alt=&quot;Meat Cuts&quot; title=&quot;Meat Cuts&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>ShopperNova</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/shoppernova/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 20:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/shoppernova/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;ShopperNova is a location-based deals app that &lt;a href=&quot;http://creativelicence.com.au/%22&quot;&gt;CLD&lt;/a&gt; made in association with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nova969.com.au/nova969/&quot;&gt;Nova FM&lt;/a&gt;&amp;mdash;one of Sydney’s largest commercial radio stations. It was one of the first apps to utilise Passbook, and enjoyed over 100,000 downloads from the App Store. Since its conception in 2012, ShopperNova allowed Nova to seamlessly move their content into the mobile space; a necessary move for radio in this day and age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ShopperNova took a slight turn in primary functionality (and the name, it became Play2Win), and has recently been sunsetted, but for roughly two years, I produced all the artwork for the app—often from very little in the way of assets—as well as regular email newsletters, website odds and ends, and other collateral.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The designs below never actually went into production. They were more of a passion project I did in my own time, as I was never fully satisfied with the UI design of the app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-approach&quot;&gt;My Approach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to create a fresher, cleaner look for ShopperNova while keeping it mostly within the brand guidelines. Choosing Montserrat over Helvetica Neue made a world of difference in the look and feel of the app, and opting for some bolder iconography and buttons really helped the designs “pop”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I kept the user flow and screen content much the same, but decided to reorganise various sections, such as the menu, so that they made more sense and improved usability. My actual role in the project essentially allowed me to user test the app to bits over two years, so I was able to gain a lot of insight into what things worked and what didn’t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/shoppernova/shoppernova.png&quot; alt=&quot;ShopperNova&quot; title=&quot;ShopperNova&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item><item><title>Glenda Graff</title><link>http://amelia.design/articles/glenda-graff/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://amelia.design/articles/glenda-graff/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;Glenda Graff is an exclusive wedding and event planner based in Sydney’s eastern suburbs. She caters to high end clients and needed a website that reflected the aesthetic of her events and was able to showcase large amounts of imagery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since Glenda is a friend, this has been a great project for me to learn and grow over the last few years. Glenda has been happy for me to take creative control and the site has functioned largely as a passion project for me where I have been able to iterate the design and make it better as I’ve gotten better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-approach&quot;&gt;My Approach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the project, I was given a logo, a color and a small mountain of images. Together we developed some content for the site and I set out to create a great design. The first iteration was certainly not the sexiest website in the world, but over time the design has evolved into something sleek and modern, showcasing lots of beautiful imagery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I built the website from scratch, using &lt;a href=&quot;http://wintersmith.io/&quot;&gt;Wintersmith&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next time I work on this project, I would like to work out a better way of loading images, as well as connecting a CMS so the client can upload imagery. There is also potential to expand the content out and include things like booking forms and more detailed service information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/articles/glenda-graff/glenda-graff-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Glenda Graff&quot; title=&quot;Glenda Graff&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item></channel></rss>